<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Sara Zapata-Marin Ph.D</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Sara Zapata-Marin Ph.D</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pollen distribution in Toronto</title>
      <link>/project/paperpollen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/paperpollen/</guid>
      <description>Summary For this project we analyzed the spatial distribution of grass, weed and tree pollen in Toronto, Canada. The data consisted of weekly measurements of pollen concentration made between March and October 2018 for 17 locations. Our main goals were to generate a predicted surface for the concentration of pollen across the season while capturing the spatial and temporal variability through the sampled period.
The exacerbation of asthma and respiratory allergies has been associated with exposure to aeroallergens such as pollen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VOCs in Montreal</title>
      <link>/project/papervocs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/papervocs/</guid>
      <description>Summary For this project we analyzed the spatial distribution of five Volatile Organic Compounds (VOCs) in Montreal, Canada. The goal for this project was to develop predicted surfaces that would be later used in health-related studies to test if the relationship between certain types of cancer and exposure to these VOCs.
We had measurements for three monitoring campaigns between 2005 and 2006 for over 130 locations in the city. Using hierarchical Bayesian models we proposed and fitted four different models that combined land-use regression and geostatistical methods to account for the potential spatial structure after accounting for the spatial covariates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
